

## The Digital Artist's Résumé

Email: <u>kironroydev@outlook.com</u>

Portfolio: https://kironroy.github.io/

Phone: (562).221.3248

## About Me

I am a digital artist that loves to problem solve and communicate with different types of people. A life long learner, my C# and Excel skills have trained me to think analytically and my job experience contributed to my people skills.

# Work Experience

#### **Census 2020 Enumerator**

Department of Commerce - Orange County, CA

August 2020 - August 2020,

Interview residents for the Census 2020 and entering data into an iPhone app Census 2020.

## Bookkeeper

Rita Roy Pediatrics

October 2010 - Present (Telecommunicate)

Bookkeeping with Excel.

Billing/Posting payments to Office Ally.

Payroll taxes for two employees with EFTPS.

Billing Information Ruby Language.

Rita Page Vue JavaScript Framework.

#### Front-end web services

**Om Imports** 

July 2011 - August 2012, July 2018 - November 2018

Product Photography. Editing photographs with Photoshop and updating the company website: Om Imports.

## **Accounting Intern**

Downey Hospital (now PIH)

July 2012 - August 2013

Entering invoices with Mediclick. Maintaining an Excel sheet that tracks purchase orders and manual invoices.

# Key Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Procreate
- Excel 2019
- C#
- Git
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Visual Studio
- Visual Studio Code
- Vectornator
- Sketch App
- SQL
- macOS bash
- Vue.js

## Education

C# Foundation Series: Modules 1 through 9

• Certificate Module 9 Certificate (Hotel Management App)

#### **SQL Basics**

• Certificate SOL Databases: From Start to Finish Bundle

#### **UCLA**

• History BA, 2005